<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="title" translatable="false">Piwigo Client - Pro</string>
    <string name="shortDesc">
Browse and alter content on the Piwigo photo gallery of your choice
    </string>
    <string name="longDesc">
Use to browse a PIWIGO photo gallery.

NOTE: EULA must be accepted on download.

This app has all features in the free version with a few others too. No adverts.

** App is now not being Actively Developed (bug fixes only) **
** If something doesn't work - email me - it'll be fixed **

See full list of features below.

Connect to servers running on non-standard http or https ports
Accept invalid (wrong host name) or self signed server certificates if required
server Certificate pinning is supported (verify certs against a local copy)
View images at a resolution optimised for your screen (or select the one you want).
Offline read only view of your server
Show and allow zoom into images of any size available on the server
View MP4 videos (others should work too, but I've not tested other formats)
Download images.
Save fully downloaded videos
Optionally exclude videos from slide-shows
Rate images and view average ratings
Upload new images or videos (can be optionally compressed)
Automatic device folder monitoring and upload of files in a background job
View, add, amend, delete Tags and Tagged images
Setting and amend permissions, description, and other details of albums and files
Add or alter albums, their permissions, description, etc
Add, view and edit gallery users
Add, view and edit gallery groups
Copy or move images around within the gallery
Select image(s) for upload using other apps and share them with PIWIGO
Special app read-only mode available to prevent any unwanted alterations to the gallery
Some control over the layout of screens on the app (use to customise for the screen on your device)

Supported server plugins : community, piwigo_privacy, videojs,user-tags.

Want something else not listed? Try the app. If it doesn't do exactly what you need. Drop me an email using the link in the app and I'll look into adding the missing feature(s).

Upcoming Changes:

The intention is to enhance the user interface progressively, and one of the users, David Klement, has kindly provided some suggestions for screen layouts going forward which I have started using from version 1.3.95 and will no doubt be taking more ideas from. The proposals are available in full:
https://api-8938561204297001672-604498.firebaseapp.com/design-proposals/index.html

Known limitations:

1. Comments are currently unsupported - you can neither see comments nor add them. If this missing feature is important to you - please talk to me.
    </string>
</resources>
