<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="preference_caching_level_values" translatable="false">
        <item>disabled</item>
        <item>memory</item>
        <item>disk</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="preference_caching_level_items">
        <item>Caching Disabled</item>
        <item>Cache to Memory</item>
        <item>Cache to Disk</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="preference_gallery_item_slideshow_image_size_array">
        <item>best-fit</item>
        <item>square</item>
        <item>thumb</item>
        <item>2small</item>
        <item>xsmall</item>
        <item>small</item>
        <item>medium</item>
        <item>large</item>
        <item>xlarge</item>
        <item>xxlarge</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="preference_gallery_item_slideshow_image_size_array_values" translatable="false">
        <item>best-fit</item>
        <item>square</item>
        <item>thumb</item>
        <item>2small</item>
        <item>xsmall</item>
        <item>small</item>
        <item>medium</item>
        <item>large</item>
        <item>xlarge</item>
        <item>xxlarge</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="preference_gallery_item_thumbnail_size_array">
        <item>square</item>
        <item>thumb</item>
        <item>2small</item>
        <item>xsmall</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="preference_gallery_item_thumbnail_size_array_values" translatable="false">
        <item>square</item>
        <item>thumb</item>
        <item>2small</item>
        <item>xsmall</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="preference_gallery_sortOrder_entries">
        <item>Resource ID</item>
        <item>Resource Filename</item>
        <item>Resource Name</item>
        <item>Number of hits</item>
        <item>Average Rating Score</item>
        <item>Creation Date</item>
        <item>Date available</item>
        <item>random</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="preference_gallery_sortOrder_entryValues" translatable="false">
        <item>id</item>
        <item>file</item>
        <item>name</item>
        <item>hit</item>
        <item>rating_score</item>
        <item>date_creation</item>
        <item>date_available</item>
        <item>random</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="server_ssl_certificate_hostname_verification_entries">
        <item>Strict</item>
        <item>Browser Compatible</item>
        <item>Off</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="server_ssl_certificate_hostname_verification_values" translatable="false">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="user_types_array">
        <item>webmaster</item>
        <item>admin</item>
        <item>normal</item>
        <item>generic</item>
        <item>guest</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="user_types_values_array" translatable="false">
        <item>webmaster</item>
        <item>admin</item>
        <item>normal</item>
        <item>generic</item>
        <item>guest</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="privacy_levels_groups_array">
        <item>Admins</item>
        <item>Admins, Family</item>
        <item>Admins, Family, Friends</item>
        <item>Admins, Family, Friends, Contacts</item>
        <item>Everybody</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="privacy_levels_array" translatable="false">
        <item>Admins</item>
        <item>Family</item>
        <item>Friends</item>
        <item>Contacts</item>
        <item>Everybody</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="privacy_levels_values_array" translatable="false">
        <item>8</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="preference_gallery_unique_id_entries">
        <item>md5sum</item>
        <item>name</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="preference_gallery_unique_id_entryValues" translatable="false">
        <item>md5sum</item>
        <item>name</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rotation_array">
        <item>Left 90 degrees</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Right 90 degrees</item>
        <item>Right 180 degrees</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="rotation_values_array" translatable="false">
        <item>-90</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>90</item>
        <item>180</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="planned_releases" translatable="true">
        <item>Release 1.3.x</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - ? German, French, other translations for the app ?"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.95</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - User interface refinements
         - Support for favorites - depends on PIWIGO API enhancement
         - ? Please email me (there is an email link in the navigation bar) to request things you need or want that this app doesn't yet do"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.94</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Possibly - allow linking the upload process to a compression routine for videos
         - Rework of the way popup messages and progress indicators are shown so they always appear - investigate using Toast messages
         - Possibly - The ability to delete an album, but not its contents (creating orphans)
         - Possibly - Orphan file management
         - Paid App Only : (Maybe) : Support for user comments
         - Paid App Only : (Maybe) : Notify user of server updates that are available"
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="release_history" translatable="true">
        <item>1.3.93.3</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - stopped call to retrieve permissions for root album
         - more resilience when displaying corrupted uploads
         - corrections in background upload job processing logic
         - update display correctly after admin user deletes album
         - toggle all selection on select files screen
         - increased resilience to possible upload failures"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.93.2</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - initially selected item not shown on folder selection
         - reported crash - when no connection profiles yet created
         - reported crash - crash processing admin list of album names
         - reported crash - crash closing dialog without selecting album
         - reported crashes - removing album"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.93.1</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - A crash on brand new install only
        </item>
        <item>1.3.93</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Paid App Only : Enable Poll a device folder and automatically upload any content found to a specified Piwigo profile (just basic functionality at present)
         Bugfix:
         - Click events not being correctly handled in album view screen"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.92.1</item>
        <item>"Paid App only:
         Bugfix:
         - Fixed tags not loading
         - Fixed control visibility not always accurate immediately after login"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.92</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Update the app to allow local piwigo session for a given action within the app
         Bugfix:
         - Better support for the community plugin
            - Guest account used for album browsing
            - Better upload support"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.91</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Bug where selected users and group memberships not displayed on re-entering select screen
         - Fix crash selecting group and user memberships with large numbers of groups or users not yet fully loaded"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.90</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Album name text size incorrectly adjusts too large on newly opened album"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.89</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Login if upload opened and no user session available
         - Bug causing crash in file selection screen
         - Changed way state is written for Certificate preference to hopefully fix unreproducible crash"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.88</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Fixed a couple of bugs completely preventing use of app on earlier versions of android. Sorry about that. Thanks for reporting the crash.
         - NOTE: Videos don't seem to play on pre LOLLIPOP android. I'll take a look at this for the next release.
        </item>
        <item>1.3.87</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Free App Only : fixed bug where advert space doubled up on file selection page
        </item>
        <item>1.3.86</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Rewrite and consolidation of list rendering
         - Rewrite of the file selection activity
         - Paid App Only : New preferences screen for up coming automatic upload job (hidden at present)
         - Paid App Only : More functionality in Tag management
         Bugfix:
         - File upload bugs (community plugin)
         - Other Bugs affecting app stability
         - Bugs in selection album / user screens"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.85</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Minor bug fixes"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.84</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Upload fails due to bug (thanks to Gerald for pointing this out)
         - Tags pages cannot be saved to state (cause crash)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.83</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Selecting upload album dropdown after navigation from root album crashes app
         - Threading bug fixed"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.82</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Paid App Only : Added support for tags (both native and with the user tags plugin)
         - Code tidy up
         - library version upgrade
         Bugfix:
         - Fixed problem where editing all album item details wasn't possible."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.81</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Stopped videos playing by default as soon as the slideshow opens.
         - Cancel an image load once the image is no longer active on the slideshow (current +- 1 image)
         Bugfix:
         - Fixed problem using video playback in a mixed slideshow of pictures and videos"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.80</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Much better memory management in image slideshow screens (fixing biggest cause of crashes)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.79</item>
        <item>"Changes:
         - Load album pages of resources when using the slideshow if not already loaded
         - Display positional index of current item within the context of the slideshow (total may change as more data loaded due to API limitation)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.78</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
         - Fixed possible race condition in app startup
         - Corrected bug introduced in 1.3.76 that could cause issues moving or deleting resources
         - Corrected race condition in the slideshow screen
         - Tweaked the slideshow state saving"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.77</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Upload screen really is accessible on physical devices again now!"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.76</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Tidied the about screen layout of release history
            Bugfix:
            - upload screen is accessible on physical devices again
            - Avoid showing stale data after user or server change while viewing upload screen
            - Avoid showing stale data after user or server change while viewing users
            - Avoid showing stale data after user or server change while viewing groups"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.75</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Improved error handling when http(s) session token expires
            - Changed app configuration - hope upload screen is accessible on physical devices again
            Bugfix:
            - NullPointer fix
            - Correct bug where albums still linked to a now non-existent image don't load correctly.
            - Correct bug where upload screen does not display on real devices"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.74</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Delete button action on upload page caused crash if job not running
            - checkboxes not being removed again following bulk album action
            - Limit state recording of slideshow pages to 0 pages (crashes still occurring)
            - UI access visibility on menu following connection profile change
            - Avoid showing stale data after user or server change while mid gallery browsing
            - Corrections to error handling of non 200 http responses"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.73</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Limit state recording of slideshow pages to 5 pages to prevent crashes"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.72</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Altered colours (likely to continue changing for a while)
            - Rounded corners of albums (Android version >= Lollipop)
            Bugfix:
            - More reuse of images loaded and better management of those loaded to reduce memory load"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.71</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Removed 3 bugs causing crashes that are probably linked to the app being placed in the background.
            - Ensure that if an upload job fails for some reason, that it is possible to clear that job without reinstalling the app. Note: Not tested
            - Files shared with the app for upload fail to appear in the upload list"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.70</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Keystore loading tested - password protected keystores may now be loaded (BKS and PKCS12 format only). No JKS after all, sorry.
            - Check for and remove any calls to Thread.sleep
            - memory use improvement for people using the share with feature
            Bugfix:
            - Crash expanding upload album dropdown on upload page before the albums have loaded"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.69</item>
        <item>"Notes:
            - Noted people are trying to load password protected keys or from password protected pkcs files
            - App crashes (that you choose to report) are the ONLY way I know there is a problem unless you email me.
            I will add an error handler to remind users of this. It sounds counter intuitive, but its sometimes best
            that I let the app crash because users almost always don't tell me when something doesn't work!
            - Most crashes are caused by running out of memory - please help me diagnose this if it occurs to you
            Bugfix:
            - crash - Race condition after file upload complete
            - crash - Upload job not found in upload intent (very odd)
            - crash - shutdown picasso kinder
            Changes:
            - Added support for loading password protected pkcs files (untested)
            - Added support for loading multiple certificates from certificate files (untested)
            - Allowed loading of keys or certificates from JKS keystore files with a .jks filename suffix."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.68</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Changed event management to correct bug where files missing from upload page when shared with the app"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.67</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Fixed bug allowing crash on resume of fragments where dialog is shown immediately  (e.g. upload)
            - Prevent user trying to create new album prior to the parent album being selected
            Attempted Bugfix (if this occurs for you, please email me saying how to reproduce this):
            - Attempt to fix bug causing crash when using back button at an unknown point in the app (a guess)
            - Attempt to fix bug on slideshow causing crash (a guess)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.66</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Updated to latest available library versions
            Bugfix:
            - Access to the user and group pages resulted in crash on older devices (no vector graphics support)."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.65</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added extra error handling around login and logout on the connection preferences page
            - Logout triggered if you change the connection profile in use
            Bugfix:
            - Added resilience for servers that don't report available image sizes in session status."
            - Fixed logout code so it sends the request to the correct url
        </item>
        <item>1.3.64</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support for multiple galleries to be configured (connection profiles in settings)
            - This allows better use of the community plugin as you can log in as guest to see your uploaded pics"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.63</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Bug in the identification of unique files for upload (filename mode only)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.62</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support for servers using file name as unique identifier for resources (new gallery preference)
            - Added support for the Log_Failed_Logins Plugin when misconfigured prepending debug text to json response
            - Added configuration preference for max number of server redirects
            - Enabled redirection configuration for the video downloads
            Bugfix:
            - Added support for servers not returning md5sums for resources
            - Ensure picasso loader always reset when altering connection settings
            - Problem retrieving trusted certificates in preferences page
            - Reduced max default server redirects when enabled to 5
            - Obscure crash in area of server response handling
            - Silently ignore a page of resources double loaded"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.61</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Prevented requests resulting in SSL Handshake error automatically retrying.
            - Ensured md5sum is treated as optional when retrieving resource information
            Warning:
            - I have noted that an assumption is made that the server is using md5sums for uniqueness tests. Be aware of this if you use the upload feature. This is existing functionality, nothing new."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.60</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Re-added defensive coding around data retrieval server calls"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.59</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Crash fix at end of successful upload that prevented delete of temporary upload album"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.58</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support for paging of users and groups
            - Altered color of checkboxes to make it more obvious when their state can be changed
            Bugfix:
            - Corrected bug where app crashes due to UI component being detached from the server response listener
            - Corrected bug retrieving resource details if resource has no name set
            - Crash on file upload if an error occurred and the upload screen wasn't shown"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.57</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Corrected bug in the proguard file stopping the released version from working."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.56</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Improved memory use when parsing messages to and from the server
            - NOTE: I've tested this change, but not comprehensively. If you do get errors, let me know.
            - Added option to clear web response cache simply when caching to disk
            Bugfix:
            - Corrected logic bug when creating a new album"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.55</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Sharing files with the app for upload doesn't always work
            - Allow community plugin users to share files on device with piwigo upload
            - Upload file progress bug causing crash
            - Bugs in file upload that caused the app to crash"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.54</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - New property 'setting' to enable clearing of all cached videos (or pieces)
            Bugfix:
            - Video not playing when caching of videos to disk is enabled"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.53</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Attempt to fix video not playing issue on Samsung S4 (released version of app only)."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.52</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support for the PIWIGO community plug-in as per user request - N.B. This plugin is NOT compatible with the pwigio_privacy plugin.
            - NOTE: that community plugin API support seems to be very poor from what I've seen so far. You get a very different experience to the website."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.51</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support for admin users to see albums they don't have explicit permission to see
            - Add support for admin users to upload to albums they don't have explicit permission to see
            - Tidied up the masonry view a bit
            Bugfix:
            - Album thumbnails now downloaded to match size of image thumbnails
            - User and groups access permissions setting of album had been broken (does no-one use this?)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.50</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Bug in video range requests prevented videos playing for some people"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.49</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Better fix for the full screen advert causing a crash"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.48</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Discovered change in google library for adverts causes crash when full screen ad is displayed. Downgraded app to android v26 until resolved."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.47</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Enable user driven retry for any failed server request at point of failure
            - Added masonry style layout (disabled by default) - user request
            Bugfix:
            - Added more defensive code to slideshow (crash reported)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.46</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Log in as a normal (non admin or webmaster) user was broken. Thanks Olivier for pointing this out!"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.45</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Updated to latest library versions and compiled for the latest version of Android.
            - Upload - recognise existing files and link to upload album (and change access permissions to those selected for this upload job).
            - Altered EULA to allow use of the app commercially
            Bugfix:
            - Fixed a couple of causes of crash (slideshow and upload)
            - Notifications not working on Oreo and above."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.44</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added "unlink from album" option for the delete of multiple resources - Will require a change to piwigo 2.9.2 to be efficient (ticket raised).
            - Improve the long click delete album functionality
            - Added warning about http hosted piwigo server
            Bugfix:
            - Update positively affected albums correctly after linking a resource to one
            - Correctly disable upload button when pressed
            - Fixed a memory leak
            - Corrected wording of album delete to reflect action"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.43</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Allow guest users (of the piwigo server) to log in again
            - Fix the unlock app dialog"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.42</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Crash in area of video cache for users of video cache created with older versions
            - Leak in request handlers could cause the queue (3) to fill and app to lock for the 5 minute timeout if login credentials aren't correct"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.41</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Build and upload a paid, advert free version, retained identical licence terms. If you wish to use the app commercially, which the EULA prohibits, please email me.
            - Added an active email link to the EULA page.
            - Added "Copy link" (to clipboard) option on download dialog
            - Checked the app works with piwigo server 2.9.2
            Bugfix:
            - Names of albums now always shown"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.40</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            Fix bug causing crash when webservice call forced to terminate early"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.39</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            Fixes bug introduced in rush to release 1.3.38 causing app to close unexpectedly."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.38</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - New dialog explaining the trusted certificate store operation
            Bugfix:
            - Auto install of trusted certificates wasn't always occurring
            - changes to shutdown code for http client to try and remove cache has been shutdown error message"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.37</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Previews are now generated for video files (upload screen)
            Bugfix:
            - Upload button correctly disabled when upload started
            - DialogBox now displays correctly on login page again"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.36</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Connection Settings: User feedback for the piwigo server address field (if missing a valid scheme)
            - Upload and Upload Settings: Check for sensible file sizes of files selected for upload (default max size to upload without warning 20MB)
            - Album Settings: Reduced the default page size for requests of album contents to 20 items per request (from 100)
            - Album Settings: Added option to allow image names to be hidden
            Bugfix:
            - Display user values for encrypted fields in the preferences correctly.
            - Upload Controls not re-enabled following job completion until re-opening page
            - Album not auto-refreshing on return from upload page (if a file uploaded while there to this album)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.35</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Altered the app icon to use one based on the material.io icons that are used throughout the app
            - Added a reference to the material.io icon set in the about page."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.34</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added code to allow release of paid for version without adverts
            - Added video mime type to list of supported types for Upload activity (where you share a file with this app)
            - Changes to the way popup messages are generated to prepare for more comprehensive alterations later
            - Confirmed the app should now support, * though I have not tested * Digest and Kerberos authentication (any realm)
            - Improved security around stored authentication information
            - Better handling of album permissions regarding presently logged in user
            - Stop CPU going to sleep (and thus terminating) background upload job
            Bugfix:
            - Fixed (and tested) Basic Authentication support (note: the credentials will be used for all realms on your server).
            - Fixed bug when disabling custom trusted server certificate store
            - Selecting trusted server or client authentication certificates in preferences didn't work
            - Fixed (and tested) client certificate authentication
            - Album not automatically refreshed after pasting copied resources
            - Errors in the handling of restarting jobs that failed
            - Errors with some upload defaults not being used correctly"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.33</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Allow restart of partially uploaded files that previously would have failed and needed manual intervention.
            - Now create and use a temporary album for upload - to ensure files are never visible to people they aren't intended for
            - Allow upload job to be recovered if the app crashes for any reason during the upload
            Bugfix:
            - Massively better memory management by changing image load code at expense of slightly fuzzy thumbnails (Fix out of memory errors)
            - Crash in albums with blank album spacers in some circumstances
            - Crash opportunity in video cache management"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.32</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Errors in proguard file following changes may well be causing app events not to be received by other app components"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.31</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Following user feedback, reduced full screen ad frequency on both upload and album browsing to show no more than once every 24 hours
            - Added banner ads to all pages
            Bugfix:
            - Missing click listener on album list item when not using large album thumbnails
            - Retry button not shown sometimes on view album page
            - User page starts now scrolled to top"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.30</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added support to select default image downloaded in slideshows (default: based on device screen size)
            - General tidy of the way server calls are made
            - Support for controlling caching of responses from the server - on disk or in memory (previously disabled)
            - Support for custom trusted certificate store (for self signed certs and or non standard root CAs)
            Bugfix:
            - All server calls are now resilient to session timeout
            - Click handler for thumbnails and images not loaded correctly
            - Playing a video prevented playing another until app restart
            - Lots of little niggles"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.29</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Allow upload of videos (change api used for upload)
            Bugfix:
            - Fixed upload of multi chunk photos again
            - App can be minimised without crashing again
            - Fixed Crash on App LowMemory warning"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.28</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Added reminder to rate the app. Will remind you once per install. Can be cancelled.
            - Tidy up the upload and create album screen
            - Overhaul of the permissions selection screens (User, Group, Album).
            - Added option to create a sub-album when viewing the album contents
            Bugfix:
            - Permissions settings wasn't working properly
            - Fixed a number of causes of crashes
            - Fixed a few bugs where screen content potentially didn't accurately reflect server content
            - Fixed a potential cause of memory leak in file upload
            - Better memory management"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.27</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Redesigned the default layout of the upload file list
            - Tweaked the appearance of the album view
            - Allow altering the way that albums are displayed (settings)
            - Shuffled the settings a bit
            - Tweaked the appearance of the upload view (configurable in settings)
            Bugfix:
            - Regression - Albums without a thumbnail were no longer supported"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.26</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Release 1.3.25 was a disaster - instant crash on most phones. Sorry!"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.25</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Link to albums file present in within slideshow details works more logically
            - Extra retry attempt to server if connection fails
            - Extra gallery setting to configure theme
            - Extra gallery setting to configure albums visible per row
            - Tidied layout of album and slideshow
            Bugfix:
            - Names of images now always shown"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.24</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Allow moving and copying files between albums
            - Allow bulk copy move and delete of files in an album
            Note: A feature of PIWIGO means that if you move the final image from an album, it remains that album's thumbnail
            BugFix:
            - Further Exception handling in server login code
            - Prevent crash if album list retrieve fails on upload screen
            - Total Photo count for sub albums incorrect
            - Large cached videos could cause crash"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.23</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Prevent access to new delete functionality if not admin user or app in read only mode
            - Corrected bug in the app Lock functionality (used when logged in as an admin)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.22</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Can change album thumbnail, both for current album and any other in the gallery
            - Can select and delete resources in bulk from an album
            - Can delete an album by "long clicking" within the parent album
            - Can now delete an album even if it contains images and or sub albums.
            Bugfix:
            - State not saved correctly on picture slideshow item
            - State not saved for create album fragment (crash on resume)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.21</item>
        <item>"Changes:
            - Opening the root album clears all app history back to the first time an album was viewed.
            - When using back button on preferences page, the root album is opened (note above change).
            Bugfix:
            - Crash on Upload page
            - Crash due to page history growing too large (it is now trimmed)
            - Hopefully fixed crash on View Album page (not certain what is causing it at the moment)
            - When returning to upload in progress, changed user makes to file upload list are not applied to running job"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.20</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Paging of album content (crash)
            - View downloaded item on Android 7+ (crash)
            - Crash if screen closed just before it triggered a call to server
            - Crash after downloading image on Android versions below 5 (Lollipop)
            - Not auto changing displayed screen after login"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.19</item>
        <item>"Improvement:
            - Added code to allow reloading an album when some or all content fails to load
            Bugfix:
            - Errors in the area of the file upload process (interaction with existing albums)
            - Back button didn't work correctly, particularly in app settings"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.18</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Crash reported on Android 5.0 on Upload screen
            - Other bugs linked to upload"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.17</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - New album load routines crashed app on some albums"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.16</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Screen overlay when back button use on first use.
            Improvements:
            - Minor tuning
            - Default to allow videos to be played (new installs)
            - New top tip"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.15</item>
        <item>Bugfix:
            - Image preview not shown on upload page
            - Crash when attempting to share images with app and it is not yet configured
            - since 1.3.4 (just reported) - Image download did not work
            - Crash when attempting to use email-to hyperlink when not logged in to server
            - Crash while rapidly traversing slideshow items
            - Client SSL certs support obviously broken (still untested)
            Improvements:
            - handling of invalid server preferences
            - paging of album content
            - Allow choice over image displayed
            - Allow greater image zoom on demand
            - Top Tips page added"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.14</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
            - Potential crash if the session times out while viewing an album / slideshow.
            Extra debug - to try and identify a crash that someone experienced on the file upload screen."
        </item>
        <item>1.3.13</item>
        <item>"Bugfix:
                - For non admin users, album permissions are incorrectly displayed and load attempted - this fails as not authorised and displays a misleading error message in album.
                - For non admin users, album edit button is displayed.
                - Not all parent album content displayed is automatically refreshed on upload to a child album"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.12</item>
        <item>Bugfix - crash caused by saving invalid piwigo server resourceUrl in the preferences
        </item>
        <item>1.3.11</item>
        <item>"Added rough but theoretically complete support for client certificate authentication (UNTESTED - Please email me if this doesn't work - I'll prioritise completing it).
            supports importing of client certificate from .p12 and .cer files.
            Bugfix - regression - where slideshow position is reset when screen is rotated
            Bugfix - regression - permissions incorrectly shown for album items
            Bugfix - regression - where slideshow shows occasional blank positions after deleting a number of items from it
            Bugfix - slideshow not in sync with gallery contents after returning from an upload operation (warning now shown)
            Bugfix - issue if deleting a slideshow item before server has had time to return the resource details (privacy details and rating).
            Bugfix - Upload of file seems to randomly "fail" stating it's already been added to the server (HTTP 500 response received from server)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.10</item>
        <item>" - Bug fixes surrounding the new functionality of uploading by sharing images.
            Bug fixes on issues that cause a crash if the app is minimised during Uploading"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.9</item>
        <item> - Hope to have fixed a bug caused when the app is left for long periods and the session is logged out. Please report the crashes still if this occurs again.
        </item>
        <item>1.3.8</item>
        <item>Bug fixes. (Mainly - Re-enabled Uploading of images)
            - Added a share-to action so you can select a file or files for upload using other apps.
        </item>
        <item>1.3.7</item>
        <item>" - Added support for adding / editing groups and their permissions
            - Fixed a number of bugs in or around the slideshow area of the app
            - Fixed a bug preventing video playback on non standard http/https ports
            - Further performance enhancements"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.6</item>
        <item>" - Added support for adding / editing users and their permissions
            - Added support for servers running schemes on non standard ports (e.g. https on port 80, or server running on port 81 etc)
            - Added support to accept invalid SSL certificates if wanted (sometimes needed when using public wifi that intercepts https traffic)
            - Prevent access to admin screens previously visited when the app is locked by using the back button"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.5</item>
        <item>" - Caching of videos is not required to allow playback now
            - Preferences now display correctly when returning to them using the back button.
            - Corrected bugs in the use of back button generally
            - Switched offset of image/album detail toggle button to be in dp (if you need px instead, please tell me)"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.4</item>
        <item>" - Firstly, apologies, this release has been a long time coming but I wanted to be sure that I had only introduced improvements
            - Reworked the PIWIGO API access to stop responses getting "lost" if the device is for example rotated while a request to the server is in progress
            - Removed several bugs that would cause the app to crash.
            - Changed file upload to allow uploading to continue in the background
            - Added local caching of video files (configurable) and the ability to save fully cached videos locally if enabled.
            - Removed image size download option for image sizes not explicitly generated on the server
            - Corrected a bug in the slideshow displayed while deleting files
            - Long click on album thumbnails and album resources invokes re-downloading of that resource (On Videos, it clears any locally cached data)
            - Fixed a number of bugs in the area of changing user sessions without restarting the app
            - Clear the back button history when a user session is changed
            - Added a gallery property to allow user correction of the positioning of the image / video details bottom drawer that slides up
            - You can drill into users and groups and view album permissions in full screen to make this easier on a small screen"
        </item>
        <item>1.3.3</item>
        <item> - Fixed a bug that was reported by a user as causing an application crash (in Release 1.3.1)
        </item>
        <item>1.3.2</item>
        <item>" - Fixed a bug that was reported by a user as causing an application crash (in Release 1.3.1)
            - Added ability to browse users and groups, view their permissions across a gallery, and delete them as wanted."
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
