<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- Android 10+
: selection of folders - permissions managed correctly.
: download of items - now works
Note: You may need to re-select your preferred download or automatic upload folder.
NOTE: I am ceasing to actively develop this app - I'll continue to support it with bugfixes intermittently though.
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- Android 10
: výběr složek - oprávnění spravovaná správně.
: stažení položek - nyní funguje
Poznámka: Možná budete muset znovu vybrat preferovanou složku pro stahování nebo automatické nahrávání.
POZNÁMKA: Přestávám aktivně vyvíjet tuto aplikaci - budu ji však nadále občas podporovat podporou oprav chyb.
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Fehlerbehebung:
- Android 10
: Ordnerauswahl - Berechtigungen korrekt verwaltet.
: Download von Artikeln - funktioniert jetzt
Hinweis: Möglicherweise müssen Sie Ihren bevorzugten Download- oder automatischen Upload-Ordner erneut auswählen.
HINWEIS: Ich höre auf, diese App aktiv zu entwickeln. Ich werde sie jedoch weiterhin zeitweise mit Bugfixes unterstützen.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- Android 10
: selección de carpetas: permisos administrados correctamente.
: descarga de elementos - ahora funciona
Nota: es posible que deba volver a seleccionar su descarga preferida o la carpeta de carga automática.
NOTA: Dejo de desarrollar activamente esta aplicación, aunque continuaré admitiéndola con correcciones de errores de forma intermitente.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- Android 10
: sélection de dossiers - autorisations gérées correctement.
: téléchargement d\'articles - fonctionne maintenant
Remarque: vous devrez peut-être sélectionner à nouveau votre dossier de téléchargement ou de téléchargement automatique préféré.
REMARQUE: je cesse de développer activement cette application - je continuerai à la supporter avec des corrections de bogues par intermittence.
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- Android 10
: selezione di cartelle - autorizzazioni gestite correttamente.
: download di elementi - ora funziona
Nota: potrebbe essere necessario selezionare nuovamente il download preferito o la cartella di caricamento automatico.
NOTA: sto smettendo di sviluppare attivamente questa app - continuerò comunque a supportarla con correzioni di bug in modo intermittente.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-Android 10
：フォルダの選択-権限は正しく管理されています。
：アイテムのダウンロード-機能するようになりました
注：必要なダウンロードまたは自動アップロードフォルダを再選択する必要がある場合があります。
注：私は積極的にこのアプリを開発するのをやめます-断続的にバグ修正をしながら引き続きサポートします。
</ja-JP>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ошибка:
- Android 10
: выбор папок - права доступа управляются правильно.
: загрузка предметов - теперь работает
Примечание. Возможно, вам придется повторно выбрать предпочитаемую папку для загрузки или папку автоматической загрузки.
ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ: я прекращаю активно разрабатывать это приложение - я буду продолжать поддерживать его периодически с исправлениями ошибок.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-安卓10
：选择文件夹-权限管理正确。
：下载项目-现在可以使用
注意：您可能需要重新选择首选下载或自动上传文件夹。
注意：我将停止积极开发此应用程序-虽然我将继续间歇性地通过错误修正来支持它。
</zh-CN>
