<en-GB>
Change:
- Strongly advise getting this update, certainly if you upload files using the app.
- Rewrite of the upload code (mostly user invisible). Readies codebase for performance enhancement
- Performance improvement implementation for vast upload data transfer speed boost
Bugfix:
- Fixes annoying bug in recent releases
- quirky bugs in the upload UI
- other assorted bugs
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Změna:
- Silně doporučuje dostat tuto aktualizaci, určitě, pokud nahrát soubory pomocí aplikace.
- Přepsat kód nahrávání (většinou uživatel invisible). Opraveno Codebase pro vylepšení výkonu
- implementace vylepšení výkonu pro rozsáhlé nahrávání dat přenosu dat
Oprava chyby:
- opravuje otravnou chybu v nedávných verzích
- Quirky Bugs v nahrávání UI
- Ostatní různé chyby
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Veränderung:
- Beratung dieses Updates dringend, sicherlich, wenn Sie Dateien mithilfe der App hochladen.
- Umschreiben des Upload-Codes (meistens Benutzer unsichtbar). Ladies Codebase für die Leistungssteigerung
- Implementierung der Leistungsverbesserung für einen großen Upload-Datenübertragungsgeschwindigkeitsschub
Fehlerbehebung:
- Fixiert ärgerlicher Fehler in den letzten Releases
- schrullige Fehler im Upload-UI
- andere sortierte Fehler
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Cambio:
- Conseje fuertemente Obtenga esta actualización, ciertamente si sube archivos usando la aplicación.
- Reescribir el código de carga (en su mayoría de usuario invisible). Readies CodeBase para mejorar el rendimiento
- Implementación de mejora del rendimiento para una vasta carga de la velocidad de transferencia de datos.
Arreglo del fallo:
- Corrige un error molesto en lanzamientos recientes.
- Bugs peculiares en la UI Subir
- otros insectos surtidos
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Changement:
- conseiller fortement à obtenir cette mise à jour, certainement si vous téléchargez des fichiers à l\'aide de l\'application.
- Réécrire du code de téléchargement (principalement utilisateur invisible). Lisibles CodeBase pour l\'amélioration de la performance
- Mise en œuvre de l\'amélioration de la performance pour une vaste amélioration de la vitesse de transfert de données de téléchargement
Correction d\'un bug:
- corrige un bogue ennuyeux dans les dernières versions
- Bugs b..."
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Modificare:
- Consiglia vivamente di ottenere questo aggiornamento, certamente se carichi i file utilizzando l\'app.
- Riscrivi il codice di caricamento (per lo più invisibile per lo più invisibile). Letture CodeBase per il miglioramento delle prestazioni
- Implementazione del miglioramento delle prestazioni per vasta boost di trasferimento dei dati di upload
Risoluzione del problema:
- Corregge fastidiosi bug nelle uscite recenti
- Bug quirky nell\'utente ui
- Altri bug assortiti
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
変化する：
- アプリを使用してファイルをアップロードした場合、このアップデートを手に入れることを強くお勧めします。
- アップロードコードの書き換え（主に目に見えない）。 Performance EnhancementのためにCodeBaseを読みます
- 膨大なアップロードデータ転送速度昇圧のための性能改善実装
バグ修正：
- 最近のリリースで迷惑なバグを修正しました
- アップロードUIのクォリキーバグ
- その他の盛り合わせのバグ
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Verandering:
- Sterk adviseren om deze update te krijgen, zeker als u bestanden uploadt met behulp van de app.
- Herschrijven van de uploadcode (meestal door de gebruiker onzichtbaar). Leestingen CodeBase voor prestatieverbetering
- Implementatie van prestatiesverbetering voor VAST UPLOAD Gegevensoverdracht Snelheidsboost
Bugfix:
- Fixeert irritante bug in recente releases
- eigenzinnige bugs in de upload ui
- andere geassorteerde bugs
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Изменять:
- Сильно рекомендуйте получить это обновление, конечно, если вы загружете файлы, используя приложение.
- Переписывайте код загрузки (в основном пользователь невидимый). Headies CodeBase для улучшения производительности
- Реализация повышения производительности для расширенного увеличения скорости передачи данных загрузки
Исправлена ошибка:
- исправления раздражающей ошибки в последние релизы
- причудливые ошибки в UI загрузки
- другие разные ошибки
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
改变：
- 强烈建议获取此更新，当然，如果您使用应用程序上传文件。
- 重写上传代码（主要是用户不可见）。 receies用于性能增强的CodeBase
- 巨大上传数据传输速度提升性能改进实施
错误修正：
- 在最近的版本中修复恼人的错误
- 上传UI中的古怪错误
- 其他什锦错误
</zh-CN>
