<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- Multimedia URIs not working for non privacy plugin users.
- video playback doesn't start if preference set not to include videos in slideshows
Change:
- there is a new setting in the connection preferences for privacy plugin uri repair
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- Multimediální identifikátory URI nefungují pro uživatele zásuvných modulů bez ochrany osobních údajů.
- přehrávání videa se nespustí, pokud je nastavena předvolba nezahrnovat videa do prezentací
Změna:
- v předvolbách připojení je k dispozici nové nastavení pro opravu URI pluginu ochrany osobních údajů
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Bug-Fix:
- Multimedia-URIs funktionieren nicht für Benutzer von Nicht-Datenschutz-Plugins.
- Die Videowiedergabe startet nicht, wenn die Einstellung so eingestellt ist, dass keine Videos in Diashows aufgenommen werden
Veränderung:
- Es gibt eine neue Einstellung in den Verbindungseinstellungen für die Reparatur des Datenschutz-Plugins uri
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- Los URI multimedia no funcionan para usuarios de complementos que no son de privacidad.
- la reproducción de video no comienza si se establece la preferencia para no incluir videos en presentaciones de diapositivas
Cambio:
- hay una nueva configuración en las preferencias de conexión para la reparación de uri del complemento de privacidad
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- Les URI multimédias ne fonctionnent pas pour les utilisateurs de plugins non privés.
- la lecture vidéo ne démarre pas si la préférence est définie pour ne pas inclure de vidéos dans les diaporamas
Changement:
- il y a un nouveau paramètre dans les préférences de connexion pour la réparation d\'URI du plugin de confidentialité
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- Gli URI multimediali non funzionano per gli utenti di plug-in non per la privacy.
- La riproduzione video non si avvia se la preferenza è impostata per non includere i video nelle presentazioni
Modificare:
- c\'è una nuova impostazione nelle preferenze di connessione per la riparazione uri del plugin per la privacy
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-プライバシープラグイン以外のユーザーに対してマルチメディアURIが機能しない。
-スライドショーにビデオを含めないように設定されている場合、ビデオの再生は開始されません
変化する：
-プライバシープラグインのuri修復の接続設定に新しい設定があります
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Bugfix:
- Multimedia URI\'s werken niet voor gebruikers die geen privacy-plug-in hebben.
- het afspelen van video\'s start niet als de voorkeur is ingesteld om geen video\'s op te nemen in diavoorstellingen
Verandering:
- er is een nieuwe instelling in de verbindingsvoorkeuren voor reparatie van de privacy-plug-in uri
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ошибка:
- Мультимедийные URI не работают для пользователей, не использующих плагин конфиденциальности.
- воспроизведение видео не запускается, если в настройках установлено не включать видео в слайд-шоу
Изменить:
- в настройках подключения появилась новая настройка для восстановления uri плагина конфиденциальности
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-多媒体URI对非隐私插件用户不起作用。
-如果首选项设置为不将视频包括在幻灯片中，则视频播放不会开始
更改：
-隐私插件uri修复的连接首选项中有一个新设置
</zh-CN>
