<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- Insufficient file permissions used, causing failing uploads
- Files downloaded not visible to other apps
- download working for both default Downloads folder, and one selected by the user
- App requested Read or Write File permissions when they weren't required.
Changes:
- New preference in app settings listing all Uri permissions held and their purpose
- New DocumentProvider exposing files downloaded in the default download location to the system file selector.
- No longer add fil..."
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- Není použito dostatečné oprávnění k souboru, což způsobuje selhání nahrávání
- Stažené soubory nejsou viditelné pro jiné aplikace
- stahování funguje jak pro výchozí složku Stahování, tak pro jednu vybranou uživatelem
- Aplikace požadovala oprávnění ke čtení nebo zápisu souboru, když nebyla požadována.
Změny:
- Nová předvolba v nastavení aplikace se seznamem všech zadržených oprávnění Uri a jejich účelu
- Nový DocumentProvider vystavující soubory stažené ve výchozím umístění ..."
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Bug-Fix:
- Es werden nicht genügend Dateiberechtigungen verwendet, was zu fehlgeschlagenen Uploads führt
- Heruntergeladene Dateien sind für andere Apps nicht sichtbar
- Download funktioniert sowohl für den Standard-Download-Ordner als auch für einen vom Benutzer ausgewählten
- Die App hat Lese- oder Schreibberechtigungen für Dateien angefordert, wenn diese nicht erforderlich waren.
Änderungen:
- Neue Einstellung in den App-Einstellungen, in der alle gehaltenen Uri-Berechtigungen und ihr Zwe..."
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- Se han utilizado permisos de archivo insuficientes, lo que provoca errores en las cargas
- Archivos descargados no visibles para otras aplicaciones
- descarga que funciona tanto para la carpeta de descargas predeterminada como para una seleccionada por el usuario
- La aplicación solicitó permisos de lectura o escritura de archivos cuando no eran necesarios.
Cambios:
- Nueva preferencia en la configuración de la aplicación que enumera todos los permisos de Uri y su propós..."
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- Les autorisations de fichier utilisées sont insuffisantes, entraînant des échecs de téléchargement
- Les fichiers téléchargés ne sont pas visibles par d\'autres applications
- le téléchargement fonctionne à la fois pour le dossier Téléchargements par défaut et pour celui sélectionné par l\'utilisateur
- L\'application a demandé des autorisations de lecture ou d\'écriture de fichier lorsqu\'elles n\'étaient pas nécessaires.
Changements:
- Nouvelle préférence dans les p..."
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- Sono state utilizzate autorizzazioni file insufficienti, che causano caricamenti non riusciti
- File scaricati non visibili ad altre app
- download funzionante sia per la cartella Download predefinita, sia per quella selezionata dall\'utente
- L\'app ha richiesto le autorizzazioni di lettura o scrittura del file quando non erano necessarie.
I cambiamenti:
- Nuova preferenza nelle impostazioni dell\'app che elenca tutte le autorizzazioni Uri detenute e il loro scop..."
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-使用されているファイル権限が不十分であるため、アップロードが失敗します
-ダウンロードしたファイルは他のアプリには表示されません
-デフォルトのダウンロードフォルダとユーザーが選択したフォルダの両方でダウンロードが機能する
-アプリは、必要のないときにファイルの読み取りまたは書き込み権限を要求しました。
変更点：
-保持されているすべてのUri権限とその目的を一覧表示するアプリ設定の新しい設定
-デフォルトのダウンロード場所でダウンロードされたファイルをシステムファイルセレクターに公開する新しいDocumentProvider。
-AndroidMediaStoreにダウンロードしたファイルを追加しなくなりました-どのファイルセレクターでも使用できます。
勧告：
-1。アプリが保持しているすべてのファイル権限を新しい設定で表示し、アプリに保持させたくないものをすべて削除します。
-2。各バックグラウンドアップロードジョブを確認し、アップロードするフォルダを再選択します
-3。サーバーからファイルをダウンロードするフォルダーを再選択します。
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Bugfix:
- Onvoldoende bestandsrechten gebruikt, waardoor uploads mislukken
- Bestanden gedownload die niet zichtbaar zijn voor andere apps
- downloaden werkt voor zowel de standaard map Downloads als een map die door de gebruiker is geselecteerd
- App verzocht om lees- of schrijfbestandsmachtigingen wanneer ze niet vereist waren.
Veranderingen:
- Nieuwe voorkeur in app-instellingen met een lijst van alle Uri-machtigingen en hun doel
- New DocumentProvider toont bestanden die zijn gedownload ..."
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ​​ошибка:
- Использованы недостаточные права доступа к файлам, что приводит к сбою загрузки
- Загруженные файлы не видны другим приложениям
- загрузка работает как для папки загрузок по умолчанию, так и для папки, выбранной пользователем
- Приложение запрашивало разрешения на чтение или запись файла, когда они не требовались.
Изменения:
- Новое предпочтение в настройках приложения, в котором перечислены все разрешения Uri и их назначение.
- Новый DocumentProvider, показывающий фай..."
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-使用的文件权限不足，导致上传失败
-下载的文件对其他应用程序不可见
-下载适用于默认的“下载”文件夹和用户选择的一个文件夹
-不需要时，应用程序请求了读取或写入文件权限。
变化：
-应用程序设置中的新首选项列出了所有保留的Uri权限及其用途
-新的DocumentProvider，将在默认下载位置下载的文件暴露给系统文件选择器。
-不再添加下载到Android MediaStore的文件-在任何文件选择器中都可以使用它们。
建议：
-1.在新的首选项中查看该应用程序拥有的所有文件权限，删除不希望该应用程序保留的所有文件权限。
-2.检查您的每个后台上传作业，重新选择要上传的文件夹
-3.重新选择文件夹以将文件从服务器下载到
</zh-CN>
