<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- Rewrite of the album, tag, and favorite sorting code because it was riddled with bugs
: If something in this area now doesn't work as you expect, please let me know.
: This should solve crashes that were occurring on the slideshow page
Changes:
- New preference to allow independent sort order reversal of child albums and resources
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- Přepište album, značku a oblíbený třídicí kód, protože byl plný chyb
: Pokud nyní něco v této oblasti nefunguje tak, jak očekáváte, dejte mi prosím vědět.
: To by mělo vyřešit pády, ke kterým došlo na stránce prezentace
Změny:
- Nová preference umožňující nezávislé obrácení pořadí řazení podřízených alb a zdrojů
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Bug-Fix:
- Schreiben Sie das Album, das Tag und den bevorzugten Sortiercode neu, da es voller Fehler war
: Wenn etwas in diesem Bereich jetzt nicht wie erwartet funktioniert, lassen Sie es mich bitte wissen.
: Dies sollte Abstürze beheben, die auf der Diashow-Seite aufgetreten sind
Änderungen:
- Neue Einstellung, um die unabhängige Umkehrung der Sortierreihenfolge von untergeordneten Alben und Ressourcen zu ermöglichen
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- Reescriba el álbum, la etiqueta y el código de clasificación favorito porque estaba plagado de errores
: Si algo en esta área ahora no funciona como esperaba, hágamelo saber.
: Esto debería resolver los bloqueos que estaban ocurriendo en la página de la presentación de diapositivas.
Cambios:
- Nueva preferencia para permitir la inversión de orden de clasificación independiente de álbumes y recursos secundarios
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- Réécriture de l\'album, du tag et du code de tri favori car il était criblé de bugs
: Si quelque chose dans ce domaine ne fonctionne pas comme prévu, veuillez me le faire savoir.
: Cela devrait résoudre les plantages qui se produisaient sur la page du diaporama
Changements:
- Nouvelle préférence pour permettre l\'inversion indépendante de l\'ordre de tri des albums enfants et des ressources
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- Riscrittura dell\'album, tag e codice di ordinamento preferito perché era pieno di bug
: Se qualcosa in quest\'area ora non funziona come previsto, fammelo sapere.
: Questo dovrebbe risolvere i crash che si stavano verificando nella pagina della presentazione
I cambiamenti:
- Nuova preferenza per consentire l\'inversione indipendente dell\'ordinamento di album e risorse secondari
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-アルバム、タグ、お気に入りのソートコードがバグだらけだったので書き直しました
：この領域の何かが期待どおりに機能しない場合は、お知らせください。
：これにより、スライドショーページで発生していたクラッシュが解決されるはずです。
変更点：
-子アルバムとリソースの独立した並べ替え順序の反転を許可する新しい設定
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Bugfix:
- Herschrijf het album, de tag en de favoriete sorteercode omdat deze vol zat met bugs
: Als iets op dit gebied nu niet werkt zoals u verwacht, laat het me dan weten.
: Dit zou crashes moeten oplossen die optraden op de diavoorstellingspagina
Veranderingen:
- Nieuwe voorkeur om onafhankelijke sorteervolgorde omkering van onderliggende albums en bronnen mogelijk te maken
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ошибка:
- Перепишите альбом, тег и любимый код сортировки, потому что он был пронизан ошибками
: Если что-то в этой области сейчас работает не так, как вы ожидали, сообщите мне.
: Это должно устранить сбои, которые происходили на странице слайд-шоу.
Изменения:
- Новое предпочтение, позволяющее независимое изменение порядка сортировки дочерних альбомов и ресурсов.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-重写专辑，标签和喜欢的排序代码，因为它充满了错误
：如果此区域的某些内容现在无法按预期工作，请告诉我。
：这应该可以解决幻灯片页面上发生的崩溃
变化：
-新的首选项允许子相册和资源的独立排序顺序反转
</zh-CN>
