<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- Tidy up of a lot of issues causing crashes across the app following the last month of changes
- Default setting for video compression corrected
- Re-added support for minimise albums
- fix videos not being detected
Changes:
- Removed option to specify which files are video playable. This is done based on file extension derived mimetype
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- Uspořádejte spoustu problémů způsobujících zhroucení aplikace po posledním měsíci změn
- Výchozí nastavení pro kompresi videa opraveno
- Znovu přidaná podpora pro minimalizaci alb
- opravit videa nebyla detekována
Změny:
- Odebraná možnost určit, které soubory lze přehrávat video. To se děje na základě mimetypu odvozeného od přípony souboru
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Bug-Fix:
- Beheben Sie viele Probleme, die nach dem letzten Monat der Änderungen zu Abstürzen in der gesamten App führen
- Standardeinstellung für Videokomprimierung korrigiert
- Unterstützung für das Minimieren von Alben wurde hinzugefügt
- Korrigieren Sie nicht erkannte Videos
Änderungen:
- Option entfernt, um anzugeben, welche Dateien per Video abgespielt werden können. Dies erfolgt basierend auf dem von der Dateierweiterung abgeleiteten Mimetyp
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- Arregle muchos problemas que causan fallas en la aplicación luego del último mes de cambios
- Se corrigió la configuración predeterminada para la compresión de video
- Soporte re-agregado para minimizar álbumes
- corregir videos que no se detectan
Cambios:
- Opción eliminada para especificar qué archivos se pueden reproducir en video. Esto se hace en función del tipo mime derivado de la extensión de archivo
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- Remédier à de nombreux problèmes provoquant des plantages dans l\'application après le dernier mois de modifications
- Réglage par défaut de la compression vidéo corrigé
- Prise en charge ré-ajoutée pour minimiser les albums
- corriger les vidéos non détectées
Changements:
- Option supprimée pour spécifier les fichiers pouvant être lus par vidéo. Ceci est fait en fonction du type MIME dérivé de l\'extension de fichier
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- Riordina molti problemi che causano arresti anomali nell\'app dopo l\'ultimo mese di modifiche
- Impostazione predefinita per la compressione video corretta
- Aggiunto nuovamente il supporto per ridurre al minimo gli album
- risolto i video che non vengono rilevati
I cambiamenti:
- Opzione rimossa per specificare quali file sono riproducibili video. Questa operazione viene eseguita in base al tipo MIME derivato dall\'estensione del file
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-先月の変更後、アプリ全体でクラッシュを引き起こす多くの問題を整理します
-ビデオ圧縮のデフォルト設定が修正されました
-アルバムを最小化するためのサポートが再度追加されました
-ビデオが検出されない問題を修正
変更点：
-ビデオ再生可能なファイルを指定するオプションを削除しました。 これは、ファイル拡張子から派生したmimetypeに基づいて行われます
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Bugfix:
- Ruim veel problemen op die crashes veroorzaken in de app na de laatste maand van wijzigingen
- Standaardinstelling voor videocompressie gecorrigeerd
- Opnieuw toegevoegde ondersteuning voor het minimaliseren van albums
- repareer video\'s die niet worden gedetecteerd
Veranderingen:
- Optie verwijderd om aan te geven welke bestanden video afspeelbaar zijn. Dit wordt gedaan op basis van het mime-type dat is afgeleid van de bestandsextensie
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ошибка:
- Устранение множества проблем, вызывающих сбои в приложении после последнего месяца изменений.
- Исправлены настройки по умолчанию для сжатия видео.
- Снова добавлена поддержка сворачивания альбомов.
- исправить видео, которые не обнаруживаются
Изменения:
- Удалена возможность указывать, какие файлы воспроизводить видео. Это делается на основе mimetype, производного от расширения файла.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-整理了导致上个月更改后整个应用崩溃的许多问题
-修正了视频压缩的默认设置
-重新添加了对专辑最小化的支持
-修复未检测到的视频
变化：
-删除了用于指定哪些文件可播放视频的选项。 这是基于文件扩展名导出的mimetype来完成的
</zh-CN>
