<en-GB>
Change:
- Strongly advise getting this update if you upload using the app.
- Rewrite of the upload code (mostly user invisible). Readies codebase for performance enhancement
Bugfix:
- Fixes annoying bug in recent releases
- quirky bugs in the upload UI
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Změna:
- Silně doporučuje dostat tuto aktualizaci, pokud nahrát pomocí aplikace.
- Přepsat kód nahrávání (většinou uživatel invisible). Opraveno Codebase pro vylepšení výkonu
Oprava chyby:
- opravuje otravnou chybu v nedávných verzích
- Quirky Bugs v nahrávání UI
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Veränderung:
- Beratung dieses Updates, wenn Sie mit der App hochladen.
- Umschreiben des Upload-Codes (meistens Benutzer unsichtbar). Ladies Codebase für die Leistungssteigerung
Fehlerbehebung:
- Fixiert ärgerlicher Fehler in den letzten Releases
- schrullige Fehler im Upload-UI
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Cambio:
- Conseje fuertemente Obtenga esta actualización si carga usando la aplicación.
- Reescribir el código de carga (en su mayoría de usuario invisible). Readies CodeBase para mejorar el rendimiento
Arreglo del fallo:
- Corrige un error molesto en lanzamientos recientes.
- Bugs peculiares en la UI Subir
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Changement:
- conseiller fortement à obtenir cette mise à jour si vous téléchargez à l\'aide de l\'application.
- Réécrire du code de téléchargement (principalement utilisateur invisible). Lisibles CodeBase pour l\'amélioration de la performance
Correction d\'un bug:
- corrige un bogue ennuyeux dans les dernières versions
- Bugs bizarres dans le téléchargement UI
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Modificare:
- Consiglia vivamente di ottenere questo aggiornamento se carichi utilizzando l\'app.
- Riscrivi il codice di caricamento (per lo più invisibile per lo più invisibile). Letture CodeBase per il miglioramento delle prestazioni
Risoluzione del problema:
- Corregge fastidiosi bug nelle uscite recenti
- Bug quirky nell\'utente ui
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
変化する：
- アプリを使用してアップロードした場合は、このアップデートを受信することを強くお勧めします。
- アップロードコードの書き換え（主に目に見えない）。 Performance EnhancementのためにCodeBaseを読みます
バグ修正：
- 最近のリリースで迷惑なバグを修正しました
- アップロードUIのクォリキーバグ
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Verandering:
- Sterk adviseren om deze update te krijgen als u uploadt met de app.
- Herschrijven van de uploadcode (meestal door de gebruiker onzichtbaar). Leestingen CodeBase voor prestatieverbetering
Bugfix:
- Fixeert irritante bug in recente releases
- eigenzinnige bugs in de upload ui
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Изменять:
- Настоятельно рекомендую получить это обновление, если вы загрузите с помощью приложения.
- Переписывайте код загрузки (в основном пользователь невидимый). Headies CodeBase для улучшения производительности
Исправлена ошибка:
- исправления раздражающей ошибки в последние релизы
- причудливые ошибки в UI загрузки
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
改变：
- 如果使用应用程序上传，强烈建议获取此更新。
- 重写上传代码（主要是用户不可见）。 receies用于性能增强的CodeBase
错误修正：
- 在最近的版本中修复恼人的错误
- 上传UI中的古怪错误
</zh-CN>
