<en-GB>
Bugfix:
- videos not identified if using privacy plugin and videos accessed from /galleries.
Change:
- app now recognises that some servers store videos under /galleries rather than /upload
</en-GB>
<cs-CZ>
Oprava chyby:
- videa nebyla identifikována, pokud se používá plugin pro ochranu osobních údajů a videa přístupná z / galerie.
Změna:
- aplikace nyní rozpoznává, že některé servery ukládají videa spíše pod / galerie než / upload
</cs-CZ>
<de-DE>
Bug-Fix:
- Videos, die bei Verwendung des Datenschutz-Plugins nicht identifiziert wurden, und Videos, auf die von / gallery zugegriffen wird.
Veränderung:
- Die App erkennt jetzt, dass einige Server Videos unter / gallery anstatt unter / upload speichern
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
Arreglo del fallo:
- videos no identificados si se usa un complemento de privacidad y videos a los que se accede desde / galerías.
Cambio:
- la aplicación ahora reconoce que algunos servidores almacenan videos en / galleries en lugar de / upload
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
Correction d\'un bug:
- les vidéos non identifiées si vous utilisez le plugin de confidentialité et les vidéos accessibles depuis / galeries.
Changement:
- l\'application reconnaît maintenant que certains serveurs stockent des vidéos sous / galeries plutôt que / upload
</fr-FR>
<it-IT>
Risoluzione del problema:
- video non identificati se si utilizza plug-in per la privacy e video a cui si accede da / gallerie.
Modificare:
- l\'app ora riconosce che alcuni server memorizzano i video in / gallerie anziché in / upload
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
バグ修正：
-プライバシープラグインを使用している場合に識別されないビデオと/ galleriesからアクセスされるビデオ。
変化する：
-アプリは、一部のサーバーが/ uploadではなく/ galleriesの下にビデオを保存することを認識するようになりました
</ja-JP>
<nl-NL>
Bugfix:
- video\'s die niet zijn geïdentificeerd bij gebruik van de privacy-plug-in en video\'s die toegankelijk zijn via / galleries.
Verandering:
- app herkent nu dat sommige servers video\'s opslaan onder / galerijen in plaats van / uploaden
</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
Исправлена ошибка:
- видео не идентифицируются при использовании плагина конфиденциальности и видео, доступ к которым осуществляется из / galleries.
Изменить:
- приложение теперь распознает, что некоторые серверы хранят видео в / galleries, а не в / upload
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
错误修正：
-如果使用隐私插件，则无法识别视频，以及从/ galleries访问的视频。
更改：
-应用现在可以识别某些服务器将视频存储在/ galleries下，而不是/ upload
</zh-CN>
